开萝尔:妈妈,爸爸,
Carol: Mom, Dad, it's a very generous offer, but,
你们很关心我,但是我不需要,
I don't I don't need to look over the dorms of Boston College to...
不需要去波士顿学院看宿舍来说服我.我已经作决定了,
to convince me. I've already made my decision,
我知道我明年要去哪……哥伦比亚大学,很近,
and I know where I want to go next year...
曼哈顿,很方便.
Columbia University, in near by and convenient Manhattan.
你们不会太失望的,是吗?
You're not too disappointed, are you?
本:一点也不!你能离开这家就够了,去哪都行.
Ben: Heck no! Anything that gets you out of the house is fine with me.
开萝尔:妈妈,爸爸,你们很关心我,
Carol: Mom, Dad, it's a very generous offer,
但是我不需要,不需要去波士顿大学看宿舍来说服我.
but I don't need to look over the dorms of Boston College to convince me.
我已经作决定了,我,我知道我明年想去哪.
I've already made my decision, and I...I know where I want to go next year.
杰森和开萝尔:好的!
Jason and Carol: Yes!!
杰森:好了,开萝尔,
Jason: Alright Carol, you're not gonna regret this.
你不用道歉,你会和我们一样爱上波士顿学院的,
You're gonna love B C as much as both of us did.
你认为我们给了她太多的压力.
And you thought we were putting too much pressure on her. Ha!
哈,她已经自己作了决定.
And she made the decision on her own.
开萝尔:对了,谈到压力
Carol: Well, speaking of pressure...
麦琪:铛铛!
Maggie: Da da!
开萝尔:那是什么?
Carol: What's that?
麦琪:波士顿学院的入学申请,我拿了来……
Maggie: The admission's application for Boston College, I took the liberty of...
杰森:好!我们填一下吧!
Jason: Hello! Let's fill that sucker out!
开萝尔:好的,爸爸,
Carol: Well, Dad, have you ever thought of the possibility that I just
你想过录取的可能性吗?
might not get accepted?
麦琪:好了,
Maggie: Yeah, right. Honey,
宝贝.凭你的成绩和你父母两位优秀的毕业生,
with your grades and two distinguished alumni as parents,
你的申请和面试只是一种形式罢了.
your application and interview are just formalities.
开萝尔:面试!
Carol: Interview!
杰森:对,如果你不想去的话,
Jason: Yeah, and if you don't want to make the trip,
他们会派人来见你,还有我们.
they'll send somebody up to meet you and meet us.
麦琪:当然,那也只是一种形式.
Maggie: Of course. But, it's just a formality.
开萝尔:好极了!
Carol: Great!
杰森:嘿,本,
Jason: Hey, Ben, wait till you hear the news.
等着听消息吧.开萝尔要去上你爸妈的学校.
Carol's gonna be going to the same college your Mom and I went to.
本:只要她离开家,别和我在一起,去哪都行.
Ben: Anything that gets her out of the house is fine with me.
开萝尔:迈克,妈妈和爸爸去了波士顿学院,
Carol: Mike, Mom and Dad went to Boston College; they met there,
我们在那相遇,在那相爱,
they fell in love there, they did God-knows-what there...
上帝知道他们他们做了什么……我是说,
I mean, if you'd just seen there faces,
如果你刚才看见他们的脸,你就会知道让他们失望是多么的难以想象.
you'd know how impossible it would have been to disappoint them.
迈克:嘿,这对我并不是一个问题.
Mike: Hey, it's never been a problem for me.
开萝尔:并且一旦我被录取,那会是,"
Carol: And once I've been accepted, it'll be, "Carol,
开萝尔,就试着上一学期",然后,
just try it for one semester."
他们会说,"呵,读完本科吧",
Then, they'll say, "ha, might as well get your undergrad degree",
然后又是,"为什么不读博士呢".
then, "why not your PHD."
迈克:嘿,离开这房子对我来说就是件好事.
Mike: Hey, anything to get you out of the house, is fine with me.
开萝尔:好,我可能只能接受了,
Carol: Yeah. I might as well accept the inevitable.
申请已经邮寄了,下一步就是面试.
The application is mailed and the interview is next.
迈克:嘿,我想我已经有办法了.
Mike: Hey, I think I've got a way out.
开萝尔:你说,你快说!
Carol: Tell me! Tell me!
迈克:好,面试的时候,
Mike: Alright, this interview deal,
你可以打嗝,发出一些难闻的气味,你就会不及格了.
you could flunk it by belching and smelling bad and stuff.
你还需要什么办法尽管说,我就在这.
You need any more ideas, you know where I live.
麦琪:你好,宝贝.
Maggie: Hi, honey.
迈克:你好,妈妈.
Mike: Hi Mom.
麦琪:哦,有块三明治真不错.
Maggie: Oh, a sandwich would be nice.
开萝尔:妈,我可以和你谈谈波士顿学院的事吗?
Carol: Ma, can I talk to you about the Boston College decision?
麦琪:哦,你的爸爸和我正想和你谈呢.
Maggie: Oh, your dad and I just can't stop talking about it either.
开萝尔:好的……
Carol: Ah, well, see...
麦琪:你知道,宝贝,
Maggie: You know, honey, when you were two,
在你两岁时,我们带你去参加波士顿学院的聚会.
we took you with us to a BC reunion.
就在广场中央,我还给你换了尿布.
I actually changed your diapers smack dab in the middle of the quad.
开萝尔:啊.
Carol: Ah.
麦琪:你爸爸和我逛了一下校园,我们梦想这一天的到来……现在真的来了.
Maggie: You know, and your dad and I looked out over that campus,
你的旅程从那块换尿布的地方就已经开始了.哦,
and we dreamed this day would come...and it's finally here.
开萝尔!!
You've come along way from that dirty diaper. Oh Carol!
我很抱歉,你想对我说些什么吗?
I'm sorry, what did you want to tell me?
开萝尔:不要忘了放芥末.
Carol: Don't forget the mustard.
麦琪:哦,好的,谢谢你,宝贝.
Maggie: Oh, right, thanks honey.
本:啊哈.我有了,我有了.嘿,
Ben: Aha. I got it. I got it. Hey, I'm a kid, not an idiot.
我是一个孩子,但不是傻子.不,那不是一种态度,
No, that's not an attitude, that's the way I feel. Good bye, yourself.
那是一种方式.再见.嘿,
Hey, Carol, some guy just called for you; says he's coming over at seven,
开萝尔,有人要打电话给你,说他七点来,如果合适的话.
if that's OK.
开萝尔:今晚?有人?
Carol: Tonight? Some guy?
本:是的,他说他来自波士顿学院.
Ben: Yeah, says he's from Boston College.
开萝尔:好的,没告诉任何人吧?
Carol: Alright, don't tell anybody about this call. OK?
本:放心.
Ben: Don't worry.
杰森:喂,电话打给谁?
Jason: Hi, who was the phone for?
本:哦,是开萝尔……那是打错了.
Ben: Oh, some guy for Carol...err...it was a wrong number.
杰森:他找开萝尔,还会号码有错?
Jason: He asked for Carol, and it was the wrong number?
本:真的!谁会打电话给开萝尔呢?
Ben: Sure! What guy would call Carol on purpose?
麦琪:开萝尔,不要忘了今晚给你和本做晚饭.
Maggie: Carol, don't forget you're making dinner for yourself and Ben tonight.
开萝尔:你们今晚要出去?
Carol: You're not going to be here tonight?
麦琪:是的,我们要去参加拉马斯聚会,记得吗?我们想带上克莉丝.
Maggie: No, we're going to our Lamars re-union, remember? We want to show you off Chrissy.
开萝尔:你们要出去!太好了!
Carol: So, you're not going to be here! Great!
杰森:不要这么激动,开萝尔,我们会回来的.
Jason: Don't be so thrilled carol, we are coming back.
开萝尔:迈克,我需要你帮忙.
Carol: Mike, I need your help.
迈克:我知道,但是我不会分身,哦,我将自己劈成两半.
Mike: I know, but I don't do electrolysis. Oh, boy, I break me up.
开萝尔:迈克,
Carol: Mike, the recruiter from Boston College is coming over tonight
波士顿学院的面试官今晚要来面试我.
to interview me.
迈克:什么面试官?
Mike: What recruiter?
开萝尔:上个星期我告诉你的,现在,
Carol: The one I told you about last week.
我有了一个计划,但是你得帮我.
Now, I figured a plan out, but you have got to help me!
迈克:为什么要我帮你?
Mike: Why have I got to help you?
开萝尔:因为!因为你是我哥哥,
Carol: Because! Because you're my brother and you love me.
你爱我.因为你需要钱,我会给你二十块的.
Because you're a scum bucket and I'll give you twenty Bucks.
迈克:行,成交.你的计划是?
Mike: Done deal. Alright, what's your plan?
开萝尔:好,实际上你给我出了主意,
Carol: Well, actually you gave me the idea when you said I should blow
你说我应该面试的时候打嗝,发出难闻的气味,搅乱这面试.
the interview by belching and smelling bad.
迈克:(嗅一下)好,但是你能打嗝吗?
Mike: (sniffing) OK, but can you belch?
开萝尔:迈克,听我说.妈妈和爸爸今晚要出去,对吧?所以,当面试官来这,我会彻底装成一个傻瓜,搅乱这面试,这样的话,我就可以去哥伦比亚大学了.
Carol: Mike, listen, OK? Right, now, Mom and Dad are going out tonight, OK? So, when this recruiter guy gets here, I'll act like a complete fool, blow the interview, and presto, I'm off to Columbia University!
迈克:好的,开萝尔,看到你为了能自己做申请决定而变成这个样子,我真难过.
Mike: Alright, Carol!! You know it saddens me to think of what a sleazemeister you could have been, if you'd only applied yourself when you were young.
开萝尔:谢谢你.你在计划中的角色是非常非常简单的.
Carol: Thank you. Now, your part in this plan is very very very very simple.
迈克:好的,对于二十块来说,已经足够了.
Mike: Well, it better be for a measly twenty Bucks.
开萝尔:好的,你找两个人扮演我们的妈妈和爸爸.
Carol: Ok, you get two people to pretend they're Mom and Dad.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
开萝尔:面试官必须要见他们,对吧?
Carol: Well, the recruiter has to meet them doesn't he?
好了,我一个小时以后下楼来见你.
Alright, now I'll meet you downstairs in an hour.
迈克:嘿,喔喔!
Mike: Hey, wow wow wow wow wow!
你要我出去,只有一个小时时间,
Come on, you expect me to go out and get a whole new set of parents
找来全新的父母.一天我也做不到……我已经试过了.
in an hour. I couldn't do that in a day...I've tried.
开萝尔:你说得对,真是开玩笑?那是不可能的.
Carol: You're right. Who am I kidding? This is impossible.
迈克:当然如果变成四十块的话,不可能也是可能的.
Mike: Of course for a forty Bucks, the impossible is possible.
麦琪:好,我们应当在两个小时以后从拉马斯聚会回来.
Maggie: OK, now we should be back from the Lamars re-union in a couple of hours.
杰森:或者,我们一看完录像带,就可以走了.
Jason: Or, whenever we run out of video tape; whichever comes sooner.
麦琪:杰森,请你帮我提一下.
Maggie: Jason, could you give me a hand here please.
杰森:哦,真的,我能有什么东西拿不了呢!
Jason: Oh, sure, like I have nothing to carry!
开萝尔:好的,你们现在很开心.
Carol: Well, you guys have fun now.
杰森:有人在做鱼子酱.
Jason: Somebody's making my tuna fiesta.
本:你们,你们知道我讨厌西班牙菜.
Ben: Come on you guys, you know how I hate Spanish food.
开萝尔:好的,本,这不是西班牙菜,它是墨西哥.
Carol: Well, actually Ben, it's not Spanish, it's Mexican.
本:哦,我完了.
Ben: Oh, well pop my pi?ata!
杰森:好了.
Jason: Alright.
开萝尔:玩得开心,你们走吧.
Carol: Have fun. Here you go. Here.
麦琪:你在抱怨你拿的东西,
Maggie: You're complaining about what you're carrying,
我可是怀克莉丝九个月啊.
when I carried Chrissy for nine months.
杰森:嘿.
Jason: Hey.
迈克:嘿,听者,他们都走了?
Mike: Hey, listen, is the coast clear?
开萝尔:迈克,你去了哪?你找到……
Carol: Mike, where have you been? Did you find...
迈克:开萝尔,来见一下西维尔医生和他的太太.铛铛!
Mike: Carol, say hello to Doctor and Mrs. Jason Seaver. Ta da!!
弗瑞德;你好,我真名叫弗瑞德.
Fred: Hi, my real name's Fred.
威尔玛:我是威尔玛,很可惜……可惜!我们没有一个叫泼波尔丝的的女儿.
Wilma: I'm Wilma, and save it...save it! We don't have a daughter named Pebbles.
开萝尔:迈克,这些人扮演我的父母!
Carol: Mike, these people are supposed to be our parents!
迈克:我没有太多的时间,明白吗?
Mike: I didn't have a whole lot of time, remember?
威尔玛:呜!这真是一个好地方!
Wilma: Ooooh! Nice place we got here!
开萝尔:迈克,说话啊!
Carol: Mike, a word!
迈克:对不起.
Mike: Excuse us.
弗瑞德;当然,你有雪利酒吗?
Fred: Certainly. You wouldn't have any sherry would you?
开萝尔:迈克,好了,也许,也许我们可以让弗瑞德收拾干净,穿件爸爸的衣服,但是威尔玛没有牙齿.
Carol: Mike, alright, maybe...maybe we can clean Fred up and put one of Dad's suits on him, but Wilma has no teeth.
威尔玛:嘿!我有牙齿,只是没有带来.
Wilma: Hey! I got teeth. I just didn't bring 'em with me, that's all.
迈克:我们今晚的计划有些变化.好?
Mike: Look, there's been a change of plans here tonight, OK?
伙计们,我们现在只需要弗瑞德来做这件事了.
Guys, it turns out that we're only gonna need Fred for this thing.
弗瑞德;我总是对你说,戴上你的牙齿.
Fred: What do I always tell ya? Wear your teeth.
迈克:听着,弗瑞德,弗瑞德,
Mike: Listen, Fred, Fred, why don't we go and take you upstairs, and...
我们上楼去,你洗洗干净,然后我来教你怎么说.
errm...get you cleaned up and then I'll coach you on what to say.
弗瑞德;你在找什么……表演的技巧?(他打了一个嗝)
Fred: What are you looking for...performance wise? (He belches)
威尔玛:哈!这是鱼子酱.
Wilma: Ha! This is Tuna Fiesta.
开萝尔:迈克,现在该演出了.
Carol: Mike, it's show time.
面试官:你好,我是比尔?杰斐逊,来自波士顿学院.
Recruiter: Hi, Bill Jefferson, Boston College.
开萝尔:你好,开萝尔?西维尔,请进.
Carol: Hi, Carol Seaver. Please come in.
面试官:谢谢你.我很抱歉,
Recruiter: Thank you. I apologize for the short notice, but...err...
通知很仓促,但是……招生办打电话给我,
I was on Long Island on personal business and when the admissions office
说他们收到你的申请,我刚好在长岛有一些私事,
called and said they'd received your sterling application,
为什么不顺路拜访呢.所以我来了.
why don't I work you in. So here I am.
开萝尔:是的,你来了.
Carol: Yep, here you are.
面试官:波士顿学院的人都很激动,因为有你这样成绩出众的人来申请.
Recruiter: May I say that we at BC are thrilled that someone of your academic
caliber has applied
开萝尔:哦,好的.请原谅我穿成这样,我晚上还得工作.
Carol: Oh, right. Please excuse the way I'm dressed, I'm working later.
面试官:我很想见见你的父母.
Recruiter: So...err... I'm anxious to meet your parents.
开萝尔:好的,只有我的爸爸在这儿,
Carol: Well, only my Dad's gonna be here,
我的妈妈,你知道的,
my Mom as you know is a news reporter and she's out of town on a
她是一个新闻记者,她已经离开这个小镇采访去了.
story.
面试官:哦,我理解.所有的新闻,都等着印刷呢,对吧?
Recruiter: Oh, I understand. All the news, it's fit to print, right?
开萝尔:实际上,那是电视新闻.
Carol: Actually, it's television news.
面试官:哦,如果你不告诉其他人,我也不会说的.
Recruiter: Oh, well, if you don't tell anybody, neither will I.
我给你看一下波士顿学院的介绍.杰斐逊先生,我的父亲.
I present to you Boston College. Mr. Jefferson, my father.
哦,喔,
Oh, wow, Doctor Seaver, it's a pleasure.
西维尔医生,很荣幸,我看你仍然佩戴着波士顿学院的校徽呢.
I see your still wearing the Boston College colours.
弗瑞德:哦,是.要点雪利酒吗?
Fred: Oh yeah. Say, can I get you a sherry?
面试官:不,谢谢.
Recruiter: No, thank you.
弗瑞德:很好,我还要点.
Fred: Great; more for me.
开萝尔:这是我的哥哥,迈克.
Carol: And this is my brother, Mike.
迈克:嘿,你!你好啊?
Mike: Hey, yo! What's up?
面试官:西维尔医生,我知道你是一位精神病学家.
Recruiter: So, Doctor Seaver, I understand that you're a psychiatrist.
弗瑞德:是的,你最好相信.
Fred: Err...yeah, you better believe it.
面试官:我明白,我很遗憾你的夫人今晚不能参加.
Recruiter: I see. I'm sorry your wife won't be joining us this evening.
弗瑞德:哦,是的,蜜琪不能来,我也很遗憾.
Fred: Oh yes, I'm sick about the fact that Micky can't be here.
面试官:蜜琪?不是麦琪吗?
Recruiter: Micky? Isn't that Maggie?
弗瑞德:呃……是的,蜜琪只是我们上床时对她的爱称.
Fred: Err...Yeah, Micky's just my pet name for her when we're in the sack.
面试官:呃……开萝尔……呃…….我们以你在中学时的成绩开始我们的谈话吧,那真的很令人吃惊.
Recruiter: Err...well Carol...err...let me begin by saying that you're high school grades are nothing more than spectacular.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thank you.
迈克:嘿,您能相信因为管教学校的原因,她拉了六个月的课,还得了6个A吗?
Mike: Hey, and can you believe she got those six straight As after missing six whole months because of reform school.
面试官:管教学校?
Recruiter: Reform school?
开萝尔:一点点误会,因为一把刀子.
Carol: A little misunderstanding over a knife.
面试官:呃……好的,开萝尔,你能说一下想去波士顿学院的原因吧?
Recruiter: Err...well Carol, what would you say is your number one reason for wanting to attend Boston College?
开萝尔:啊,好的,那很简单.我不可能进入像哈佛和耶鲁这样的常青藤联盟学校,所以,我盘算一下,为什么不去波士顿学院呢?
Carol: Ah, well that's easy. See, I could never really cut it in a real Ivy League college like Harvard or Yale; so figure, why not cruise through BC?
迈克:说实话,如果像我爸爸说得那么容易,算上我吧.
Mike: Heck, if it's as easy as my pop says it is, then heck, sign me up too.
面试官:西维尔医生,这就是你对开萝尔所说的波士顿学院?
Recruiter: Doctor Seaver, is this what you told Carol Boston College is like?
弗瑞德:是的,说实话,
Fred: Well, to tell you the truth Bob,
鲍勃.
I don't remember much about the actual classes;
那些上的课我已经不记得了,那时候我和麦琪正着迷于彼此的身体呢.
me and Maggie were pretty much into discovering our bodies back then.
本:爸爸,我赢了,我赢了,就像你说的一样.
Ben: Dad, I did it. I did it. Just like you told me to.
弗瑞德:好孩子,呃,呃,呃.
Fred: Adda boy! Er, er, er..
开萝尔:本!
Carol: Bennie!
本:爸爸!我揍了那个小家伙.
Ben: Man! I punched the snot out of that little kid.
我想我甚至把他的牙齿都打松了,我做得很棒吧,爸爸?
I think I even knocked Carol: couple of teeth loose. Isn't that great dad?
弗瑞德:是的.
Fred: Yeah.
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
弗瑞德:是的.
Fred: Yeah.
迈克:就像你说的那样,对吧,爸爸?
Mike: Just like you say, right pop?
弗瑞德:哦,好的.很好,
Fred: Oh right. Right. Like I always tell you son.
像我一直教导你的,儿子.
Never be scared to second punch someone,
不要害怕打第二拳,哪怕她们是低年级的女生.现在,
just cos they are a girl in a lower grade.
出去吧,你这个小混蛋.嗨,
Now get the hell out of here, you little scum bum. Hey, kids hu?
孩子们?听着,
Listen, if you've got any problems getting the little girl in,
如果我录取不了的话,说一声,我会给你们钱的.
say the word and I'll slip you a couple of C notes.
面试官:什么?
Recruiter: What?
弗瑞德:好的,那么三百块.
Fred: Alright. Three hundred bucks then.
面试官:小姑娘,我希望你能申请其他学校,
Recruiter: Young lady, I hope you made applications to other colleges,
因为你进入波士顿学院的几率已经为零了.再见了.
because the odds of you coming to B.C are zero. Zilch. Zip. Good evening.
弗瑞德:是我说了什么吗?
Fred: Was it something I said?
迈克和开萝尔:成功了!
Mike and Carol: Yeah!
开萝尔:我们成功了,我们成功了!
Carol: We did it, we did it!
迈克:好的!弗瑞德你太棒了.喔喔!太好了!
Mike: Alright! Fred you were great. Woo hoo! Alright!
弗瑞德:现在,该谈一谈二十块钱了.
Fred: Now, I uh, believe there was some talk of twenty bucks.
开萝尔:我马上去拿.
Carol: I'll go get it right now.
迈克:好的,在楼上.去吧,爸爸!
Mike: Alright, it's upstairs. Come on. Dad!
弗瑞德:什么?
Fred: What?
杰森:你是谁?
Jason: Who are you?
弗瑞德:我?
Fred: Uh, uh, me?
迈克:这是,杰斐逊博士,波士顿学院的面试官.
Mike: Uh, this is, uh, Dr. Jefferson. The recruiter from Boston College.
开萝尔:我给你介绍我的父亲,杰森?西维尔.
Carol: I'd like you to meet my father, Jason Seaver.
弗瑞德:你的名字是?
Fred: And your name is?
杰森:我是杰森?西维尔.
Jason: I'm, uh, Jason Seaver.
弗瑞德:哦,哦!
Fred: Oh. Oh!
迈克:好的,杰斐逊博士一直在等你回来进行这次面试.
Mike: Yeah, Dr Jefferson was waiting to start the interview till you guys got here.
杰森:没人知道这事啊?
Jason: Nobody knew about this?
迈克:哦,本知道了这消息.他忘了很大家说了,就像平时一样.
Mike: Oh well Ben took the message. And well, he messed it up again, as usual.
弗瑞德:这个小混蛋.
Fred: Little scum bum.
迈克:听着,你们为什么不先把孩子放上楼呢,我们要开始面试了?
Mike: So listen, why don't you guys go and take the baby stuff upstairs, and we'll get this interview started?
麦琪:好的.
Maggie: Ok.
杰森:好的.我们会马上下来,博士.
Jason: Alright. We'll be right down doctor.
麦琪:是的,给我一点时间放下这个小家伙.
Maggie: Yes, just give me a moment to put the baby down.
你为什么穿成这样?
Whys are you dressed like that?
开萝尔:为了把鱼子酱做得更鲜美些.
Carol: To, um, make the tuna fiesta more festive.
弗瑞德:把20块给我吧,我得走了.
Fred: So lay that twenty on me, and I'll just be moseying on.
迈克:听着,弗瑞德,
Mike: Listen. Fred, Fred,
你愿意酬劳加倍吗,再扮演一个角色?大学面试官.
how would you like to double your money for another part? A college recruiter.
弗瑞德:这是一个挑战!好吧.
Fred: A challenging dual role! Ok.
迈克:好的.
Mike: Alright.
开萝尔:迈克,你觉得这样明智吗?
Carol: Mike, do you think this is wise?
迈克:你还想怎么做?
Mike: What else do you want to do, hu? You want to tell them the truth?
你想告诉他们实话?
Look mum and dad are expecting an interview,
妈妈和爸爸有多期待这场面试,
so we're going to give them an interview.
所以我们给他们安排一次面试.你会得到一封拒绝信.
You are going to get a rejection letter.
我们已经,
We already took care of that,
所以妈妈和爸爸也没有办法,
so this way mum and dad are none the wiser and you get to go to
你就会去哥伦比亚大学.
Columbia.
弗瑞德:我听说南美所有东西都很迷人.
Fred: I hear all of South America is just lovely.
杰森:我今天想穿我的波士顿学院的校服.
Jason: I wanted to wear my Boston College blazer today.
麦琪:不行.袖口有肉汁.
Maggie: No you wouldn't. It has gravy on the sleeve.
杰森:没人会注意的.
Jason: No one would notice.
麦琪:我会.
Maggie: I would.
杰森:好吧,我今晚本想穿我的波士顿学院校服的,
Jason: Well I wanted to wear my Boston College blazer today,
但是更聪明的脑袋获胜了.
but wiser heads prevailed.
麦琪:我是……
Maggie: Hi, I'm...
弗瑞德:蜜琪,我知道.
Fred: Micky, I know.
麦琪:不,麦琪.
Maggie: No, Maggie.
弗瑞德:哦,蜜琪不是你的爱称?
Fred: Well isn't Micky his pet name for you?
杰森:不,不是.
Jason: No. No, it isn't.
弗瑞德:我肯定是在哪听说过,不管怎样,很高兴见到你.
Fred: Hu, I could have sworn I heard that somewhere. Well whatever. Nice to meet you.
杰森:博士,你要喝点什么吗?
Jason: So doctor, can I get you anything?
弗瑞德:来点雪利酒还不错.
Fred: Uh, a sherry would be lovely.
杰森:好的,雪利,雪利.
Jason: Great. Sherry. Sherry.
麦琪:呜
Maggie: Uh...
麦琪和弗瑞德:在橱柜里.
Maggie and Fred together: In the cabinet.
开萝尔:可能,只是猜一下.
Carol: Probably, just a lucky guess.
杰森:抱歉,已经喝完了.来些别的,行吗?
Jason: Sorry, I'm all out. Can I get you something else?
弗瑞德:当然.
Fred: Ah sure.
杰森:什么
Jason: What.
弗瑞德:像你说的,来点别的.
Fred: Like you said, anything else.
麦琪:杰斐逊博士,一通知就来安排面试,
Maggie: So, doctor Jefferson,
这正常吗?
is it normal to schedule these interviews on such short notice?
弗瑞德:正常?
Fred: Uh, normal?
迈克:好的,妈妈,
Mike: Uh, oh yeah yeah mum, see Doctor Jefferson said that, uh,
听到杰斐逊博士所说的吗,
he was just in town on personal business when the school called him and
学校通知他,问他是否能够安排开萝尔面试时他刚好在这镇上办点私事.
asked if he could schedule Carol in.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
开萝尔:是的,很难相信吧?
Carol: Yes, yes. Is that so hard to believe?
麦琪:不是这意思,宝贝,放松点.
Maggie: It isn't honey. Just relax.
弗瑞德:好的,我们开始吧.
Fred: Well, let's get started. Ahhhh!
好的,开萝尔,
Well, uh, anyway Carol, I have to tell you, as a straight A student,
我必须告诉你,像你这样的全A生,
that this interview is just a formality.
面试只是一种形式,尤其有两个优秀毕业生的父母.
Especially with two distinguished graduates as parents.
杰森,我知道你是一位直肠病学家?
Uh, Jason, I understand you are a proctologist?
杰森:嗯,精神病学家.
Jason: Uh, psychiatrist.
弗瑞德:哦,
Fred: Oh, that's very different.
那很不同.开萝尔,
Uh Carol, what's your number one reason for wanting to attend Boston
你想去波士顿大学的首要原因是什么呢?
University?
麦琪:不是波士顿学院吗?
Maggie: Uh, Isn't it Boston College?
弗瑞德:很明显,你们没有读过毕业生快报.我们正扩大规模,成为一所完全大学.开萝尔,继续吧.
Fred: Well it's obvious that you haven't read the alumni fliers. We are expanding into a full university. Carol, go on.
开萝尔:好的,我听说课程很有挑战性,
Carol: Well, I hear that the course work is very challenging,
学院也很重视社会活动.
and that the academics are stressed over by social activities.
弗瑞德:你考虑过专业吗?
Fred: Uh hu. Um, have you thought about a major yet?
开萝尔:实际上我正在计划……
Carol: Well actually I was planning on...
弗瑞德:我猜一下,你想追随你父亲的足迹来学习,是吗?
Fred: Let me guess. You are going to follow in your old mans footsteps and study, uh, pedietry?
杰森:精神病学.
Jason: Psychiatry.
弗瑞德:对不起.这是开萝尔的面试,对吧?
Fred: Excuse me. I believe this is Carol's interview. OK?
杰森:好的,对不起,但是我觉得这个面试的整个基调有点不一样.
Jason: Well excuse me, but I'm finding the whole tone of this interview to be, unusual to say the least.
开萝尔:杰斐逊博士,如果你没有其他问题的话,
Carol: Doctor Jefferson, if you don't have anymore questions,
我想结束这次面试了.很高兴见到你.
I have taken up enough of your time. It was a pleasure meeting you.
弗瑞德:西维尔医生,如果你想让她录取的话,没问题,我有一个办法.几张纸币,放在我的口袋里.
Fred: Doctor Seaver, if you want to see your girl get in, no problem, I've got a way to go. A couple of notes, right in my pocket.
杰森:不!
Jason: NO!
弗瑞德:好的.那么一百块.
Fred: Alright. A hundred bucks then.
杰森:你再说一遍.
Jason: I beg your pardon.
弗瑞德:好,我要50.
Fred: Ok. I'll take five.
杰森:听着,我不知道……
Jason: Listen, I don't know what...
弗瑞德:不管你给多少.
Fred: Whatever you got in your pocket.
本:嘿,你怎么还在这儿?
Ben: Hey, what are you still doing here?
麦琪:还!!!
Maggie: Still!
(门铃响)
(Door bell)
杰森:谁也别走.
Jason: Don't anybody move.
这儿发生的一些事很奇怪,
Something very strange is going on around here,
我得弄明白.
and I'm going to find out what it is.
我知道我错了最后几次学院聚会,
Now I know I've missed the last few college reunions,
但是我知道我的母校还没成为这样一个所在……
but I know that my old school hasn't become a place...
面试官:我冲出这个难受的屋子,忘了自己的文件夹了.
Recruiter: I rushed to get out of this nut house, forgot my pop up.
杰森:你是谁?
Jason: Who are you?
面试官:对不起,西维尔医生,
Recruiter: Excuse me. And frankly doctor Seaver,
我要亲自向上级报告这场令人反感的安排.
I am personally going to speak to the regions about this repulsive display.
麦琪:西维尔医生!
Maggie: Doctor Seaver!
杰森:他不是西维尔医生.我才是西维尔医生,你到底是谁?
Jason: That's not doctor Seaver. I'm doctor Seaver. Now who the hell are you?
面试官:比尔?杰斐逊,来自波士顿学院.
Recruiter: Bill Jefferson from Boston College.
麦琪:不,你不是.他是,你不是.
Maggie: No you are not. He is. Aren't you?
杰森:你的校服上不会有肉汁吧?
Jason: That wouldn't be gravy on your sleeve, would it?
弗瑞德:哦,肉汁.可能的.
Fred: Oh gravy. Could be.
杰森:开萝尔,
Jason: Carol, I can't believe that you went to all that trouble,
我不敢相信是你弄出了所有的麻烦,只是因为你害怕对我们说,
just because you were afraid to tell us that you didn't want to go to
你不想去上你妈妈和我上过的学校.
the same school that your mum and I went to.
开萝尔:我也不信.
Carol: Me either.
麦琪:杰森,我对你说过,你对她施加了太多的压力.
Maggie: Jason, I told you that you were putting far too much pressure on her.
开萝尔:他把太多的压力给了我!妈妈,
Carol: HE put too much pressure on me!
当你们告诉我你们带我去波士顿学院,
Mum, when you told me that you took me to Boston College and changed my
在广场给我换尿布,
diaper right in the quad, and you got all weepy,
你们都很动情,我害怕伤了你们的心.
I was afraid of breaking your heart.
杰森:哦,开萝尔.你是说你妈妈和我已经创造了一种氛围,使得你不能告诉我们你的感受?
Jason: Oh Carol, come on. Are you implying that your mother and I created an atmosphere in which you could not tell us how you felt?
开萝尔:我没有暗示,我只是照直说.
Carol: I'm not implying it. I'm flat out saying it.
麦琪:你导演了这场游戏,
Maggie: So you went through this whole charade just so you wouldn't hurt
你不害怕伤害我们的感情吗?
our feelings?
开萝尔:是的,如果你看到真相的话.
Carol: Yes. And if you look at it in that light.
我的欺骗是,是因为爱.
My deception was, was an act of love.
麦琪:别掩饰.
Maggie: Don't push it.
开萝尔:不,妈妈.
Carol: Yes mum.
杰森:好的,我不敢相信我们给了开萝尔太多了的压力,
Jason: Well I can't believe that we were putting all that pressure on
甚至都没有意识到.
Carol and didn't even realize it.
麦琪:是的,克莉丝,
Maggie: Yeah. Chrissy, you can go to any college you choose.
你可以去你选择的任何大学.你不必整个国家挑最好的,波士顿学院.
You don't have to pick the best one in the nation, Boston College.
杰森:很好,麦琪.
Jason: Nice Maggie.
威尔玛:你,谁!你们的鱼子酱真好吃.
Wilma: Yoo who! Your tuna fiesta was delish.
杰森:你是谁?
威尔玛:刚才我是麦琪?西维尔,一位记者.
00:21:27,300
Jason: Who are you? Wilma: For one brief shining moment I was Maggie Seaver, journalist.